Where is the key…
钥匙在哪儿…
Found it.
找到了
Ouch!
好痛
The heck.
讨厌
Phew.
我躺
Nice.
好喝
Right, what do I need to see Ms. Makima for?
对了 是要找真纪真小姐干吗？
Never mind.
算了
Water…
水
Why are you at my place?
你怎么会跑来我家呢？
Did I bring you here?
是我带回来的吗？
I feel dizzy. What the hell?
头好晕 怎么搞的？
Oh right. You like Ms. Makima, don't you?
对了
My head's spinning.
头昏眼花
You shouldn't like her.
别喜欢那种臭女人了
Jeez, Aki too.
讨厌 阿秋也是
Why does he have to act so shy?
还害羞成那样
Boo… Moo…
讨厌 哞…
Cow.
牛
Let's do it.
来做吧
Do…
要…
Do what?
要做什么？
Sex.
性行为
Arms up.
比个“万岁”
That's right.
好
Good boy.
乖孩子
Should I do this?
确定要做吗？
My first kiss was supposed to be with Ms. Makima.
本来初吻要献给真纪真小姐
That's right.
好乖喔
But I gave it to a woman with a mouth of vomit.
却被这女人的呕吐物玷污
Do I really want my first time to be taken by the same one?
被这种女人夺走第一次没关系吗？
Yes!
好
Good boy.
很乖
Let's take these pants off too.
下面也脱掉吧
There's something in your pocket.
口袋里好像有东西耶
A Chupa Chups? It's dirty!
珍宝珠棒棒糖？好脏喔
Denji…
淀治
Denji, are you okay?
淀治 还好吗？
Want some fresh air?
要不要去外面透透气？
I bought nausea medicine from the supermarket.
我在超市买了解酒药
Take it with water before bed.
记得睡前一定要兑水吃掉
Ms. Makima, I…
真纪真小姐 我…
I had a crappy first kiss.
得到了狗屎一般的初吻
Even if I kiss different women from now on,
就算我以后会跟很多女生接吻
I'll think of the taste of vomit
每次亲下去的时候
every time I do it.
一定会想起呕吐物的味道吧？
Open your mouth.
嘴巴张开
You probably won't ever forget the taste of vomit.
呕吐物的味道大概一辈子都忘不了
But don't worry.
但是不要紧的
From now until your death,
现在开始 直到死去的那一刻
you'll experience all kinds of first tastes.
你会尝到各种初体验的滋味
You won't have time to remember the taste of vomit.
根本没有时间想起呕吐物味
So your first indirect kiss
总之第一次间接接吻的味道
is the taste of a cola-flavored Chupa Chups.
就是珍宝珠棒棒糖可乐口味呢
Sorry, Pochita.
抱歉 波奇塔
I bet you wanted to do it too.
你也想做色色的事吧？
But I…
但是我…
I want to save it for Ms. Makima.
我的第一次还是想留给真纪真小姐
Until I kill Gun Devil.
等我杀死枪之恶魔
Until then, I…
在那之前…
Morning, Denji.
淀治 早安
Feeling up to breakfast?
有胃口吃早餐吗？
Eating while looking down at people is the best.
一边俯视人群一边吃饭就是好吃
Denji.
淀治
I got so drunk last night, I don't remember a thing.
昨晚我喝醉了 什么都不记得
Did I do anything to you?
我有没有对你乱来？
Like I'd do it with a vomit lady.
谁会跟呕吐女做那档事？
I decided my first time's gonna be with Ms. Makima.
我已经决定第一次要给真纪真小姐了
Thank god.
那就好
I'd get arrested if I made a move on a minor.
要是对未成年出手 我会被逮捕的
You are a strange one.
淀治你真奇怪
Most people would get uncomfortable and leave now.
普通人在这种状况下都会尴尬地离开
So, Denji, you like Ms. Makima too?
话说回来 你也喜欢真纪真小姐吗？
Yes, I do.
我超喜欢她
Even if she's got a crappy personality?
就算她的性格差到爆也喜欢吗？
Yes.
喜欢到爆
Okay then.
决定了
I'll set you up with her.
我来撮合你跟真纪真小姐吧
Really?
真的假的？
Yes.
真的
Denji, how about we form a secret alliance?
淀治 我们要不要私下结盟？
I'll help you get with Ms. Makima.
我会帮你跟真纪真小姐牵线
And you help me with Aki.
你来帮忙撮合我跟阿秋
What do you like about that guy?
你喜欢那家伙什么地方？
His face.
脸蛋
All right, I'm in.
好啊 我赞成
Let's do this alliance.
来组成同盟吧
So, we are no longer senior and junior from now.
那么今天起我们不再是前辈和晚辈
Let's be friends.
来当朋友吧
Come over for breakfast once in a while.
偶尔过来吃早餐吧
And bring that Fiend and Aki.
带魔人跟阿秋一起过来
Do you think Ms. Makima would come too?
真纪真小姐愿不愿意来呢？
When will we arrive in Kyoto again?
我忘了几点抵达京都来着？
In 30 minutes.
还有30分钟
I'll buy a boxed meal then.
那我就买个铁路便当吧
You have a luncheon at one, miss.
请别忘了1点还有饭局
I'll make room by then.
我会在那之前让肚子变饿的
I don't really want to meet with the Kyoto bigwigs.
真不想见京都那群大人物
They are all so scary.
所有人都很恐怖
I'd rather have my lunch in a relaxed mood.
我只是想要以平静的心情用餐
The drinks yesterday were delicious.
昨天的酒真好喝
This is Team C…
这里是C组
Commence operation.
开始
What's that noise?
那是什么声音？
You don't know? How dumb!
你竟然不知道 太蠢了吧
It's the sound of taiko drums.
那是太鼓声
Is there a festival?
办祭典吗？
Oh right.
对了
You two really didn't mate last night?
你们两个昨晚真的没交配吗？
Denji is actually a gentleman.
淀治其实是个绅士喔
I can't believe you can eat the ramen here.
真亏你们吃得下这间店的拉面
Doesn't it taste terrible?
不觉得难吃死了吗？
Who are you?
你谁啊？
Tastes fine to me!
我倒是觉得很好吃
Don't speak to me as if you know me!
不准你随便跟老子讲话
I see you can't judge the quality of food.
看来你们分辨不出味道的好坏
You can't help it though.
这也无可奈何
It's said that if you only eat the same thing in your childhood,
听说小时候只吃同一种味道的东西
your palate will be unrefined as an adult.
长大后舌头会变迟钝
And an unrefined palate lowers your happiness.
舌头迟钝的话 幸福感也会随之下降
I'm very happy!
老子幸福得很
Let's go.
我们走吧
My grandpa was the kindest man in the world.
我爷爷是全世界最温柔的人
He brought me to fancy restaurants all the time.
常常带我去很贵的餐厅吃美食
He was yakuza, but he had principles.
虽然他混黑道 却是正义的黑道
You might call people like him
像他那样的人
a necessary evil.
可谓是“必要之恶”
He's only killed a few women and children.
杀掉的妇孺屈指可数
He'd buy me anything I wanted with the drug money.
我想要什么 他都会拿卖毒品赚的钱买给我
He was a good man
是个人见人爱
whom everybody loved.
充满江户男儿气概的好人
You loved him too, right? Denji?
淀治 你也喜欢他吧
What are you getting at?
混蛋 你想干吗？
Do you know him?
你认识他吗？
Gun Devil wants your heart.
枪之恶魔想要你的心脏
-Samurai Head! -Kon!
武士头
Aki Hayakawa…
早川秋…
You put something monstrous in my mouth.
你竟然往我嘴里塞不得了的东西
It's neither human
既非人类
not devil…
亦非恶魔
Power. Stop Himeno's bleeding.
帕瓦 快帮姬野前辈止血
A nail?
钉子？
Fire!
打
Three.
三
Two.
二
Fire!
打
One.
一
I've had enough of that creepy thing.
竟敢用那种恶心的东西
Curse! Kill him!
卡斯 杀了他
Zero.
零
How's Himeno?
姬野前辈呢？
We'd better take her to a doctor now.
最好尽快带去看医生
That guy…
那家伙…
He had a gun.
竟然用了枪
But only police officers and Devil Hunters
在日本除了警方或恶魔猎人
can obtain guns in Japan.
明明不可能拿得到枪
Gun Devil wants your heart.
枪之恶魔想要你的心脏
We should get Himeno medical treatment first.
总之先帮姬野前辈处理伤势…
Your Curse Devil.
诅咒恶魔
Run that nail through someone enough times and they'll die.
只要用那个钉子钉对方几次就会死
Am I right?
我猜得没错吧？
Nice moves on your part.
你的身手挺利落的嘛
Where did you come from?
你从哪里冒出来的？
Are you with him?
是那家伙的同伙吗？
How did you lose?
你怎么输了？
I had my guard down. I really had my guard down.
我太大意 真的太大意了
Well, kill him then.
那就赶快杀了他
He's still alive.
他还活着
The Devil Hunters' suits are sturdy.
恶魔猎人的制服特别坚固
Finish him off.
给他致命一击
Leave me. Go save Aki.
别管我了 去救阿秋
No way.
不可能
I can't even see his moves.
老子根本看不清他的动作
Ghost…
幽灵…
I refuse.
我拒绝
That girl is scary.
那女人很恐怖
I will give you all of me.
我愿意献出我的全部
So let me use all of you.
让我使用你的全部吧
Aki can cry.
阿秋还能落泪
Devil Hunters get so used to death
恶魔猎人过于习惯死亡如影随形
that they eventually stop crying.
会渐渐哭不出来
But Aki cries very often.
但是阿秋动不动就会哭
When his newbies died,
他负责照顾的新人死掉时
he'd hide away and cry, and it's very interesting.
他还躲起来偷哭 真的很有趣
It must be a really good feeling
若能得到他的思念与泪水
to have someone care and cry for you.
一定会很高兴吧
Aki…
阿秋…
Don't die.
你别死喔
When I die…
当我死了…
I hope you can cry for me.
希望你能为我哭泣
Snake, swallow it.
蛇 整个吞了
Return.
回去